<placelist name="astana">
    <places>
	    <place id = "shatyr">        
	        <name>Khan Shatyr</name>
	        <description>Khan Shatyr Shopping and Entertainment Center is a new symbol of the capital of Kazakhstan, the first and the Only Lifestyle center in Astana that features world class shopping and entertainment under the same roof. Designed by famous British Architect, Lord Norman Foster, Khan Shatyr is the biggest tent in the world and also is the biggest shopping center in Kazakhstan. The main idea of Khan Shatyr is to create an atmosphere of comfort and antidote to the stress of daily life with the variety of greenery and fresh flowers. “Khan Shatyr” is located on the New Astana Center Axis which is also called “the Millennium Axis” with magnificent views of the Presidential Palace. On weekends the number of visitors reaches 30,000 people per day. Many world brands as Zara, New Yorker,Massimo Dutti, GAP, Bershka etc. represented in Astana for the first time. The sand of the beach has been flown out from the Maldives and under floor heating gives the natural beach feeling when walking on the sand.Khan Shatyr organizes different events on weekends, conducts lotteries and arranges various activities for guests in the central area called the atrium.</description>
	        <latitude>51.132614</latitude>
	        <longitude>71.402745</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
	    <place id = "triumf">
	        <name>Astana Triumph</name>
	        <description>The housing estate “Astana Triumph” has a place of honor among the best architectural projects of Kazakhstan capital.  The monumentality and majesty, power and specificity are the distinctive features of this housing estate. The unforgettable shadowgraph of the 39-floor housing estate “Astana Triumph” is observable from any part of the city. On the 37th and 39th floors, there are observation sites open for viewing the whole city. This complex is unique in Kazakhstan because of not only its architecture, but also its infrastructure. There are halls for celebrating the family events, mini-markets, boutiques, and hotel with a restaurant in the complex. The pride of “Astana Triumph” is sport center with gym classes and 25 m long swimming pools. The swimming pool is located on the different part of the building.</description>
		    <latitude>51.140198</latitude>
		    <longitude>71.415189</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
	    <place id = "congresshall">
	         <name>Congress-Hall</name>
	        <description>Congress-Hall was built in 1963 and was named as 'Tselinnik's Palace'. In 1998, the building was reconstructed and renamed to 'Congress-Hall'. It contains a concert hall that can host up to 2500 people simultaneously. Nowadays, Congress-Hall is mostly used for hosting different social and cultural events, such as concerts, exhibitions, fairs, etc.</description>
		    <latitude>51.164010</latitude>
		    <longitude>71.422304</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
	    <place id = "shabyt">
	        <name>Kazakh National University of Arts</name>
	        <description>Kazakh National University of Arts was created on the basis of the Kazakh National Academy of Music. The idea of the opening of this institution belongs to the head of the state, Nursultan Nazarbayev. The uiversity provides educational, research and performance opportunities, cultural and educational activities at all fields of arts. Kazakh National University of Arts offers seven (7) school-college programs, twenty (20) undergraduate, and sixteen (16) graduate programs. The University has six faculties: music, traditional arts, theater, film and television, choreography, and social sciences, humanities and arts. Talented young people from urban and rural areas, low-income families and orphans receive special attention and support from the institution.</description>
		    <latitude>51.123004</latitude>
		    <longitude>71.472695</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
	    <place id = "vokzal">
	        <name>Railway Station</name>
	        <description>This is the railway station of Astana. Here, you can buy tickets and go by train to many destinations, not only within Kazakhstan but to other countries too.</description>
		    <latitude>51.195755</latitude>
		    <longitude>71.409752</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
	    <place id = "nuniversity">
	        <name>Nazarbayev University</name>
	        <description>Nazarbayev University is an autonomous research university located in Astana, the national capital of Kazakhstan. Founded as a result of the personal initiative of the President of Kazakhstan, Nursultan Nazarbayev, it is an English-medium institution, with an international faculty and staff. The acceptance rate for undergraduate programs is 1:8.5. All undergraduate students attend the university free of charge, and students in good standing receive a stipend, while the faculty-to-student class ratio is 1:9.

				Nazarbayev University is legally linked to both the Nazarbayev Intellectual Schools and the Nazarbayev Endowment Fund, all of which are dedicated to promoting educational reform in Kazakhstan.</description>
		    <latitude>51.090560</latitude>
		    <longitude>71.398144</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
	    <place id = "pyramid">
	        <name>Palace of Peace and Reconciliation</name>
	        <description>The Palace of Peace and Reconciliation was designed by the British architects Foster and Partners (lead design). Turkish architectural firm Tabanlıoğlu Architects undertook construction information packages for the Foster design and engineers Buro Happold undertook lead structural and services design. The Foster team was led by architects Nigel Dancey, Peter Ridley and Lee Hallman. Sembol Construction undertook a Design and Build contract, and were ultimately responsible for the final details and finishes, some of which varied considerably from the Foster and Tabanlıoğlu (Tabanlioglu) intent. Auditorium and performance equipment design was by Anne Minors Performance Consultants and acoustics by Sound Space Design.</description>
		 	<latitude>51.123150</latitude>
		    <longitude>71.463526</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
	  	<place id = "bayterek">
	        <name>Bayterek</name>
	        <description>Bayterek, is a monument and observation tower in Astana, Kazakhstan. A tourist attraction popular with foreign visitors and native Kazakhs alike, it is emblematic of the city, which became capital of the country in 1997.</description>
			<latitude></latitude>
		    <longitude></longitude>
	    </place> 
	    
	    <place id = "defence">
	        <name>Ministry of defense of Republic of Kazakhstan</name>
	        <description>This is it. Nothing special =)</description>
			<latitude>51.124756</latitude>
		    <longitude>71.429012</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
	    <place id = "keruyen">
	        <name>Keruyen</name>
	        <description>Shopping mall.</description>
			<latitude>51.127963</latitude>
	 		<longitude>71.425190</longitude>
	    </place>
	    
    </places>
</placelist>